And then the thing
that I put in there--
the thing that I put in there
that modified the network
is called the network modifier.
So you can see on this
graph that what you've got
is your bridging,
the bridging there
that's going between
two network formers.
And then you've got
these atoms that
are hanging out near a place
where you've broken a bridge.
So those would be modifiers.
Those are called
network modifiers.
These are just terms that
you will hear and see
when you think about glass--
network formers,
network modifiers.
The chemistry that you introduce
is modifying the network,
and it's what is done in
many, many different ways
with many, many
different [INAUDIBLE]
to change the
properties of glass.
And so here's the
curve that shows
you another kind of important
way of looking at this.
And I don't need you to
remember all of these terms,
but I want to show
you because this
is how glass is engineered.
Remember, today the topic is
how do we change the properties?
We talked about
the cooling rate.
Now we're talking
about adding chemicals.
And so now you're going
to work with the glass
to do something with it.
If you're going to do that,
this is one of the first plots
you'll look up.
And it shows you-- it
plots the temperature.
This really doesn't
work at all--
the temperature on one axis--
so that's like the x-axis--
and on the y-axis is the
viscosity because now
that's the property that we're
changing, right, the viscosity?